

# BYRON RODRIGUEZ

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER FULL STACK DEVELOPER



## CONTACT



#### Phone

+502 3882-4965



#### **Email**

byron303@gmail.com



#### Address

Panajachel, Guatemala



## Linkedin

Byron Rodriguez Aragon



## **EDUCATION**

- Full-Stack Developer
  4Geeks Academy 2023
- Meta Social Media Marketing Specialization
  Meta and Coursera 2022
- Google Digital Marketing and E-Commerce Certificate
- Google and Coursera 2022
- Bachelor in Clinical
   Psychology
   Universidad Panamericana
   2015



## **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Spanish



# **ABOUT ME**

I have an educational background in clinical psychology, but digital marketing and sales have been the main focus of my professional career. Over the last two years, I've been focusing on learning for professional growth and recently graduated as a full-stack developer from a programming boot camp at 4Geeks Academy.



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Social Media ManagerHomes Guatemala

Caribbean

2016 - 2021

Social Media Manager and Marketing Coordinator: Community Manager. Content creator. Meta Ads. Video Editing. Email Marketing. SEO and Copywriting.

Sales Supervisor - XeroxRoyal Caribbean International

2014-2016

Supervisor for Customer Service Sales Representatives Onboarding Trainer and Special Services for Royal

Recruitment - Travel Coordinator 2010 - 2013Capgemini

Travel and recruitment coordinator for onboarding process and human resources in North America.



# MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Digital Marketing	Sales
Meta Ads Manager	Customer Service
Social Media Manager	Project Management
Front-End Development	Amazon Listing Optimization
Back-End Development	Amazon PPC
SEO	Email Marketing